（水滴の垂れる音）
（地鳴り）
Girls' Last Tour
♪～
It's so dark.
（ユーリ）暗い 暗い
暗い
Iiit's soooo daaaark.
（ユーリ）暗い～
Shut it.
（チト）うるせえ
（ユーリ）ん？
Sorry.
ごめん
It's okay.
いいよ
（ユーリ）あっ
Then, can I turn on the lantern?
じゃあ ランタンつけていいですか
No.
ダメ
Awww.
そんな…
Save it.
（チト）節約しろ 給油施設だって
次 どこにあるか分からないんだぞ
We don't know where we'll find
the next refueling station.
Well, we've been in the dark for a while,
so my eyes might've gotten used to it.
（ユーリ）
でも まあ… ずっと暗闇だから―
目が慣れてきたかも
We haven't seen the light of day in a while now.
（チト）もうずっと
日の光を見てないからね
Don't even know how many days it's been.
何日たったかすら…
But seriously, where are we right now?
いや ホント
どこにいるんだろうね 私たち
How'd we get into this place?
なんで こんな所にいるんだっけ
C'mon, Yuu, who do you think it was
who said they wanted to go into the hole?
ユー お前な―
あの穴に入ってみようとか
言ってたのは誰ですか？
（ユーリ）あっ…
I think it was you, Chi?
ちーちゃんだっけ？
（チト）お前だよ
It was you.
Come on, that's an old saying, isn't it?
（ユーリ）あれは ほら
古い言葉にもあるじゃん 確か…
Doesn't it go, "I wish I could just climb into a hole"?
“穴があったら入りたい”って
Does it mean it that literally?
（チト）そういう意味の
言葉だっけ？ それ
In either case, we've gotta find a way out.
（チト）
とにかく出口を見つけないと
We don't have that much food left, huh?
（ユーリ）
食べ物もあんまりないしね～
Well, even if we get outta here,
we don't know if we'll find food.
まあ 出たとこで
食料が手に入るか分からないしね
あ…
What's gonna happen to us, huh?
（チト）
どうなるんだろうね 私たち
When will we get to the top of...
ハァ… いつになったら
一番上に…
Hey.
ん？ ねえ
（いびき）
ハァ…
（ブレーキの音）
（いびき）
Guess I'll sleep, too.
（チト）私も寝よう
ふんっ うう～っ
ああ～
（いびき）
（足音）
（荷台に乗る音）
（ユーリ）うう～ん
What's the soup like?
（ユーリの寝言）
It's so smooth...
あい～ スープったって
どんな感じでえ～…
No, it's so thick...
あ… サラサラ トロトロ
うう…
（ユーリの寝言）
（ユーリのいびき）
（チト）ハァ…
So warm.
あたたかい…
（おなかの鳴る音）
I'm hungry.
おなかすいた～
♪～
（銃撃音）
（銃声）
（チト）あ…
（何かをしゃぶる音）
I'm cold...
（チト）う… さむ…
ハァ…
（何かをしゃぶる音）
（あくび）
（ユーリ）むぐむぐ…
（チト）ああっ…
ふん～っ
（ユーリ）むむ～っ
（チト）ふんっ！
（ユーリ）んんっ
（チト）ううっ うう…
（ユーリ）んーっ…
（チト）ハァ…
（ユーリ）
もぐもぐ うんうん…
うん もごもご…
（風の音）
あ…
There's a breeze!
風が吹いてる
Hey, wake up!
ねえ 起きて
（ユーリ）あっ うっ あっ…
C'mon! Yuu!
（チト）おい ユー
（ユーリ）うっ ぐっ…
うゆゆ…
（チト）んっ…
（たたく音）
（ユーリ）うあああっ…
Yeah. If we go the way the wind's blowing...
（チト）そう
風が吹くほうに進んで行けば…
...we'll find a way out?
出口があるってこと？
Yeah.
（チト）そういうこと
There.
おいしょ
はあ… んっ
あ～ あ～ う～ん…
Well?
（チト）どう？
That way.
あっち
Okay.
（チト）よし
Now it's that way.
次はあっち
（チト）分かった
Got it.
あ…
（ユーリ）ああ
Light...
（チト）光だ
（２人）ああ～
♪～
（２人）う…
（２人）わあ～
（２人）うあ～
Wow!
すごい！
It's so bright, Chi!
明るいよ ちーちゃん！
（チト）う… ううっ…
It was nighttime...
夜だったんだ
（ユーリ）んん～
（おなかの鳴る音）
Hey, since we finally made it outside,
let's have some soup, c'mon!
（２人）はっ
ねえ せっかく外に出たんだし―
スープ飲もうよ スープ
（チト）んあっ…
Fine, just to celebrate getting out of there.
じゃあ
出られた記念ということで
Alright, food!
（ユーリ）やった～ ごはん！
Gotta be good now, right?
（ユーリ）もういいんじゃない？
Yeah.
（チト）そうだな
（ユーリ）ほお～ フフーン
（チト）フーッ フーッ
Here.
はい 最後の１缶だからな
It's our last can.
Right!
うん アチッ！
Hot!
（２人）フーッ フーッ
はあ～っ おいし～い
So good!
はあああああ…
I never knew nighttime was this bright.
（ユーリ）知らなかったね
夜がこんなに明るいなんて
That's because we were in that
dark cavern that whole time.
（チト）ずっと
暗い穴の中にいたからね
It made us sensitive to light.
光に敏感になってるんだよ
So what's gonna happen to us when the sun rises?
じゃあ これで日が昇ってきたら
どうなっちゃうの？
We'll burn to death.
焼け死ぬ
（ユーリ）うわ～っ ううっ…
（チト）んあっ… うう～
Shut up!
うるさい！
（ユーリ）あ…
あ？
（２人）わあ…
♪～
Starry Sky
War
Hit.
ヒット
（銃声）
Miss.
はずれ
Huh?
ありゃ
Alright, last one.
じゃあ ラスト
You can keep on going if you want.
もっと撃ってもいいよ
あ…
（銃声）
Hit.
（チト）ヒット
（銃声）
Hit.
（チト）ヒット
You wanna shoot, Chi?
ちーちゃんも撃つかい？
No, I'm good.
いや 私はいい
You're a terrible shot, anyway.
（ユーリ）ヘタクソだもんね
Oh, shut up.
うるさいな
You don't carry a weapon?
ちーちゃんは武器持たないの？
I don't need one.
いらないよ そんなの
（ユーリ）ん…
う～ん あっ…
But there are so many.
たくさんあるのに…
Most of them are just junk.
（チト）ほとんどゴミでしょ
But I guess I could go look for one.
でも まあ もう少し
探索してみようか
It doesn't have to be a weapon.
We might find something we could use.
（ユーリ）武器じゃなくてもさ
使えるものがあるかもしれない
Maybe we'll find food.
ごはん 落ちてないかな～
No, if we're looking for food here,
いや～ ごはんは…
we'll either find something like rations, or find...
レーションみたいなものなら
あるいは…
Machine gun.
機関銃
Shells.
砲弾…
Tank.
戦車
（チト）ん？
Hey, you think a tank tastes good?
ねえ 戦車っておいしいかな
Give it a try.
食べてみれば？
Actually try it.
あ～…
（チト）ホントに食えよ
…んっ！
It's like a big weapon graveyard.
（チト）まるで武器の墓場だ
People long ago didn't have enough food, either.
（ユーリ）昔の人も
食糧不足だったんだよね
So why'd they build all these weapons?
なんで武器ばっかり作ったの？
If they'd preserved food instead of making weapons,
our lives would be so much easier.
武器じゃなくて保存食を
たくさん作ってくれれば―
私たちも楽できたのに
Well, they had their own problems, you know.
まあ いろいろ事情が
あったんでしょ
Like war.
戦争とか
あ…
Wow! A plane!
すごい 飛行機だ！
（２人）わあ…
Did it really fly?
（ユーリ）飛んでたのかな
（チト）昔はね
A long time ago, yeah.
I wanna fly.
飛んでみたいな
（チト）無理だろ
That's impossible.
You wanna fly too, right, Chi?
ちーちゃんも飛びたいだろ？
（チト）いや 全然
Nope, not at all.
（チト）んんっ… ううっ… んっ
ううっ… うっく…
Is this a weapon, too?
（ユーリ）これも武器なのかな？
（チト）うっ くっ…
I dunno.
ううっ どうだろう… うっ
But it was probably a bomber or something...
でも たぶん爆撃機とか…
そういう…
（ユーリ）よっ
（チト）お…
War means killing one another, right?
戦争って殺し合うんでしょ？
なんでそんなことするんだろうね
Why'd they do that?
Dunno. Their interests probably didn't
coincide with... the other side's!
（チト）さあ？
相手と自分の利害が―
一致… い… い…
しなかった… り…
う… うあっ
（チト）ん？
So like, if there are three people,
but only enough food for two...
たとえば３人いるのに食糧が
２人分しかないみたいな時に―
I bet that's when you've gotta
get your weapon and fight.
武器を取って戦うしか
なくなるんだよ きっと
Same now, same then...
今も昔も変わらず…
Huh?
ふ～ん
There's a lotta different kinds.
いろいろあるなあ
あっ
ん… よっ…
Look, Chi, this looks real powerful!
ちーちゃん 見て これ
強そう
Put that down.
捨てなさい
We don't need guns.
銃なんていらないよ
（ユーリ）ああっ…
There's something else we could use
way more than that... there!
それより使えるのが…
あった
Explosives.
（ユーリ）爆薬
（チト）そうっ
Yup. We can use them to move stuff
in our way or break down walls.
これがあれば障害物をどけたり
壁を壊したり
There's a whole lot.
いっぱいあるね
（チト）うん
Yeah.
We'll take as much as we can...
積めるだけ積んで…
Hey, Chi, what's this?
（ユーリ）あれ
ちーちゃん これは？
Dunno.
ん？ 何だろ
（２人）ん？
（ユーリ）あ？
（チト）うん…
（ユーリ）んんっ？
Rations!
レーションか
おお～！
（チト）うあっ
Let's grab them.
Okay!
運ぼう
（ユーリ）うげっ…
うん！
（チト）おおっ…
（ユーリ）おっ… つう…
Ready, up!
（２人）せえの…
（ユーリ）よっ
ハァ…
（ユーリ）ハァ…
（チト）ハァ…
（ユーリ）ふっ
（チト）うあ…
うう…
Ready, go!
せーの！
（２人）えいっ！
（チト）うあ… う…
Nope, it's not gonna fly.
ダメだ～ やっぱり飛ばないや～
We don't need to fly, jeez.
飛ばなくていいって
ハァ… ううっ うわっ…
That's too bad.
残念だな
（チト）全然
Not at all.
（ユーリ）えいやっ！
（チト）うわあっ あっ…
Look, it can totally fly!
ううっ…
（ユーリ）ほら やっぱり飛ぶよ！
It won't!
（チト）飛ばないっての
（ユーリ）えいっ！
（チト）うっ… うわあっ
（ユーリ）やあっ！
（チト）う… う… うわああっ
We flew!
（２人）うわあーっ
（ユーリ）飛んだ！
（落ちる音）
（おなかの鳴る音）
I'm hungry.
（ユーリ）おなかすいたね
（チト）ああ
Yeah.
Here's your half.
はい ユーの分
Thanks.
ヘヘ～ ども
It's good.
うん！ おいしい
Says it's chocolate flavored.
チョコ味らしいよ
No idea what chocolate is, though...
チョコが何なのか知らんけど
（ユーリ）んっ
（食べる音）
あっ
There's one more left.
あと１本
A pack of five? An odd number...
５本入りか 奇数だね
So we'll split it in half and...
じゃあ 半分こ…
Hey!
あっ… おいっ
はっ
Don't move.
動かないで
What are you doing?
何のつもりだ
I'm taking it.
これは私がもらう
えっ…
I see. I should've carried a weapon too, huh...
なるほど 私も武器を
持っておくべきだったか
Yep.
そう
This is war.
つまり これが戦争
Hey! You actually ate it!
あっ！ ホントに食いやがった！
Why, you!
この野郎！
（ユーリ）あっ！
Hey, Yuuri!
おい ユーリ！
（ユーリ）痛っ！
Ow!
（チト）ううっ
（ユーリ）うっ ううっ…
エヘヘ～ ヘヘ
（チト）ああっ…
エヘヘッ へへへへへ… ヘヘッ
えっ？
Ow!
（ユーリ）痛っ！
You little, you little!
Ow, ow!
（チト）このっ このっ
（ユーリ）いたたっ 痛っ 痛っ…
Ow, ow!
You little brat!
That actually hurts!
ホントに痛いってばあ
（チト）このっ このー！
That was the last one!
C'mon, Chi!
この～ 最後だったんだぞ～
（ユーリ）アハッ… ちーちゃん
You little, you little brat!
（チト）この～！
（ユーリ）おっ うっ ちーちゃん
Chi, jeez!
（ユーリ）ハァ～ッ アハハハ…
（チト）ハァ… ハァ…
（ユーリ）フフッ ハハッ…
ハハハハハ…
ハハッ ハハッ ハハハハ…
That was yummy.
あ～ おいしかった！
J-just you wait.
お… 覚えてろよ
♪～
（チトとユーリの荒い息）
I moved around too much and now I'm hungry.
♪～
（チト）動いて よけい腹減った
（チトとユーリの荒い息）
ハァ… あ…
おあ…
The snow's yummy, too.
雪もおいしいよ
（ユーリの食べる音）
Having to eat snow of all things...
雪を食べなくちゃならないなんて
ホントに 戦争ってやだね
War really is the worst.
（チト）ハァ…
ああ…
ふんっ
（ユーリ）んぐーっ！
ううううう…
（チト）ハァ～ッ
（ユーリ）うぐぐぐぐ…
Look who's talking.
お前が言うな
ううぐぐぐ… うう～っ…
ぷはーっ
♪～
（ユーリ）ん…
（チト）うう…
（ユーリ）とおっ！
♪～